♪Looking in the mirror,
my temples have turned white♪
♪Taking off the hairpins and makeup,
shedding the disguise♪
♪A cold face♪
♪With two lines of tears♪
♪If an actor could gain pity♪
♪The audience offers sincere words♪
♪Perhaps the story could be changed♪
♪The storyteller says♪
♪This mortal world is full of turmoil♪
♪Within sight but beyond reach♪
♪Yet I still don't want to give up♪
♪Don't let the memory be hollowed out♪
♪Don't make me ridiculous♪
♪Some vows turn into smoke
and fade away♪
♪Even the leaves know when autumn comes,
but you don't even know me♪
♪Imprisoned in plight,
yet still full of passion♪
♪I mock this absurd and entangled love♪
♪How can I bear to let go♪
=Whispers of Southern Song=
=Episode 1=
Tell me, where is the Buddha Head?
(Rongqing Troupe)
Everyone in Fengcheng knows
that your fiancée, Miss Jiang,
always hangs around
with that actor Rong Xiaonan.
(Xu You'an, Governor's adopted son)
Xu the Demon,
now everyone calls you
the Young Marshal Cuckold.
Mr. Rong,
I've searched all over Fengcheng,
but couldn't find anyone
with the same button.
(Jiang Chun'er)
(Daughter of Chamber of Commerce President)
I failed your trust.
(Rong Xiaonan, Actor of Rongqing Troupe)
Miss Jiang, don't be sorry.
I am an orphan.
The one who holds the other button
is my only family.
I am already grateful
that you are willing to help me.
Since he won't talk,
then cut off one of his fingers
and make him write it out.
Go to Rongqing Troupe.
Mr. Rong.
- Mr. Rong.
Everyone knows you are my woman.
Instead of being my wife,
you'd rather marry this actor?
He is indeed quite good-looking.
No wonder he has you mesmerized.
This chapter of "A Garden Stroll"
talks about the story of Du Liniang
longing for free and beautiful love.
Under the pretext of investigating
the theft of the Buddha Head,
you declined my father's invitation
a few days ago.
A month has passed,
yet you found no clues.
Why do you have time to come here today?
Of course, to catch the adulterer.
Miss Jiang, do you want
to be like Du Liniang,
pining away to death for love?
Our engagement is set,
so you should keep to your place.
If not, I will shoot him dead
right in front of you
and put an end to all your desires.
Don't, I just love watching opera.
Mr. Rong and I have never
crossed any boundaries.
(Rong Huaiqiu, Head of Rongqing Troupe)
He's dead!
Master!
Jade Buddha Head?
(Master's death must be related
to this Jade Buddha Head.)
(By touching objects to glimpse images,
maybe I can see who killed Master.)
I will never tell you
the real Buddha Head's whereabouts.
Put down the Jade Buddha Head.
It was you. You killed my master!
Nonsense!
This matter concerns
the stolen treasure of Fengcheng.
Take all members of Rongqing Troupe
to the Governor Mansion for interrogation.
Hold on.
Mr. Rong was just performing opera.
What crime has he committed?
There's a body is on the stage.
Everyone here is a suspect.
If you try to stop me,
I will kill him now.
Move aside.
Miss, let's go back
and ask Master for help.
Move aside!
Miss.
(Xu Fan, Governor of Fengcheng)
Don't you think Young Marshal's
appearance at the troupe today
is too coincidental?
Your plan was to find
the Buddha Head's whereabouts.
(Adjutant Zhao of Governor Mansion)
But Young Marshal has always
harbored misgivings
about Xiaosheng Society.
I mean no offense.
I'm just worried that he might ruin
your business with Xiaosheng Society.
If a dog can't be tamed, just kill it.
Stealing the Jade Buddha Head
and killing Head Rong.
Mr. Rong, won't you confess?
You are the murderer.
How dare you frame me!
I will definitely kill you
to avenge my master.
How dare you slander me?
Don't you even know
who you are slandering?
Mr. Rong, have you heard my nickname?
Xu the Demon.
This blood-activating powder can
make wounds bleed over and over
until they fester.
The pain is so unbearable
that you'll wish to die.
How can the top Southern Song star
in Fengcheng be so pathetic?
How did you seduce women?
So you framed me
because you are jealous of me.
How ridiculous.
You really flatter yourself.
In my eyes, you are
just an uncastrated eunuch.
I just want to know the truth
of the Jade Buddha Head case from you.
You, the murderer,
want to know the truth?
Don't you fear that your misdeeds
will bring you retribution?
(He doesn't seem to be faking it.)
(But why is he so certain
that I am the murderer?)
The Rongqing Troupe
is full of vicious bandits.
Unequal distribution
of spoils led to murder,
making the Buddha Head damaged.
And Rong Xiaonan confesses his crimes.
Foster Father.
The truth hasn't come out yet,
I'm afraid...
In Fengcheng, what I say is the truth.
This is a memorial tablet
for you after you die.
Stop pretending!
You're the real villain here.
You'd even cover for this lackey
and clear him of murder.
Lackey?
Are you seeking death?
That Jade Buddha Head is fake.
Why would I kill Master who raised me
for a fake Buddha Head?
Tell me, where is the real Buddha Head?
Sir!
Miss Jiang sent an invitation
to Governor,
saying it concerns
the distinguished guests.
(To Governor)
Governor.
(From Jiang Chun'er)
Treat his wounds.
It's too noisy.
No need to keep the rest
of the Rongqing Troupe.
Kill them all.
Mr. Rong, you're really something.
How dare you call me a lackey?
Now to save you, the Xiaosheng Society
requests to watch you perform.
Mr. Rong, you'd better perform well
if you want to live.
Of course, I will perform
to shake the Governor Mansion to its core
and drag it down to its doom.
Young Marshal.
Finding the Buddha Head is important,
(Adjutant Sun of Governor Mansion)
but you don't need to come in person.
Not just that.
I need to find the answers
to my questions.
Young Marshal,
nothing unusual.
These sleeve arrows, caltrops,
and cross-shaped darts
are all assassination weapons.
Normally, they shouldn't
appear in an opera troupe.
Has the authenticity of the Buddha Head
on the corpse been verified?
Indeed, as Rong Xiaonan said, it's fake.
The murderer would definitely know
whether the Buddha Head is real.
Rong Xiaonan must be
connected to this case.
But from the way Foster Father acted,
it seems he knew the Buddha Head is fake.
Do you suspect
the Governor is also involved?
Just now I almost killed Rong Xiaonan,
yet he still didn't confess
to killing Head Rong.
But if Foster Father wants
to kill someone, he can just do it.
Why went through all this trouble?
For now, we need
to find out the real Buddha Head.
Yes.
(Zhuzi, Young Rong Xiaonan)
You didn't practice well.
Master, I'm sorry.
- I will practice hard.
- Get up.
Xiaonan.
Performing is like living.
To stand high,
you must keep your composure.
Hold steady.
Master!
- Master, don't leave me!
- Master!
- Don't leave me!
No!
Mr. Rong, are you looking for this?
♪As if it were fate♪
♪Deliberately playing tricks♪
♪We miss each other♪
♪Creating a turbulent drama♪
♪And a bizarre♪
♪Anonymous legend♪
♪The plot twists and turns♪
♪Play out over and over again♪
♪Waiting to be discarded♪
♪And you are like a moth to the flame♪
♪Refuse to submit♪
♪I can't bear to blame you♪
♪There are always too many♪
♪Helpless situations♪
♪Overwhelmed by time♪
♪Even if I have questions♪
♪I harbor desires♪
♪Nowhere to find answers♪
♪People come and go♪
♪I'm still all alone♪
♪Wandering around♪
♪Fortunate to have you with me♪
♪Go through the entanglement♪
♪If longing♪
♪Turns into dust and smoke♪
♪How can I be at ease♪
♪Having walked through prosperous times♪
♪And travelled around the world♪
♪Scars all over me♪
♪If longing never fades♪
♪Burns still hot♪
♪Let it turn into dust and smoke♪
♪After half a lifetime of loneliness♪
♪In the next life♪
♪Entangle with you again♪